Welcome back.
So in this section, we are going to create a Android service manager or Java file from the ideal.
Okay.
So it'll be using Android studio for that.
So I have Android studio open all the way here and I how we should see your code over here.
Okay, so what I'm going to do is, first of all, just go to file and create a new idea, okay?
And I will just name it as I.
Android service manager.
Okay.
And then click on Finish.
So it created this file.
And this is the file that created it under an ideal folder or not.
And then I'll just go ahead and quickly rebuild it and just make sure everything is fine.
So Build is finished and it's fine.
So now if you go to Java generator, you have.
Sorry.
Here.
Yeah.
And on this one.
So here you have the interface like this.
And here you may have got a setup class as well.
Okay.
So.
So this is not what exactly we want.
So we need this function, this interface to be here.
So I will do is will just copy this print android and paste it over here.
Okay.
And then just let's rebuild it.
So now if I come home and I have to bring Android function or I can't.
Okay, then.
So now let's copy this file.
And we still.
Okay.
So we have now our.
So we have now our Android service manager torch our entity, and we already had the ideal.
So now we have all the resources to go ahead and implement the Android service.
So let's do that in the next session.
Thank you.